David E. Lilienthal Papers, 1900-1981 (bulk 1950-1981 ): Inventory MC148
EADs for public policy collection from import batch
- Series 18: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1905 October 19-1981; 208 boxes; 2 items
  - Subseries 18O: 1979-1981, 12 boxes
    - Garces Giraldo, Diego, 1979; 1 box (Box 544)
    - Gilinsky, Victor, 1979; 1 box (Box 544)
    - Glick, Virginia, 1979; 1 box (Box 544)
    - Golden, William T, 1979; 1 box (Box 544)
    - Graham, Katharine, 1979; 1 box (Box 544)
    - Greeneye, Mrs. Lawrence, 1979; 1 box (Box 544)
    - Gulick, Luther, 1979; 1 box (Box 544)
    - Harper & Row, 1979; 1 box
      - Re Atomic Energy: A New Start, by David E. Lilienthal, 1979; 1 box (Box 544)
    - Harvard Law School, 1979; 1 box (Box 544)
    - Haynes, William F., Jr, 1979; 1 box (Box 544)
    - Heckscher, August, 1979; 1 box (Box 544)
    - Heffner, Richard D, 1979; 1 box (Box 544)
    - Herken, Gregg F, 1979; 1 box (Box 544)
    - Hettinger, A.J., Jr, 1979; 1 box (Box 544)
    - Hoover Institution, 1979; 1 box
      - Stanford University, 1979; 1 box (Box 544)
    - Hough, Henry B, 1979; 1 box (Box 544)
    - Re Hoyt, Palmer, 1979; 1 box (Box 544)
    - Hughes, Richard J, 1979; 1 box (Box 544)
    - Hun School of Princeton, 1979; 1 box
      - Hydro-Electric Power, 1979; 1 box (Box 544)
    - (1 of 3), dates not examined; 1 box (Box 545)
    - (2 of 3), dates not examined; 1 box (Box 545)
    - (3 of 3), dates not examined; 1 box (Box 545)
    - Institute for Advanced Study, 1979; 1 box (Box 546)
    - International Basic Economy Corporation, 1979; 1 box (Box 546)
    - Re Iran, 1979; 1 box (Box 546)
      Includes papers on projected book by David E. Lilienthal
    - Jackson, Henry M, 1979; 1 box (Box 546)
    - Janeway, Eliot and Elizabeth, 1979; 1 box (Box 546)
    - Jesselson, Ludwig, 1979; 1 box (Box 546)
    - Jones, Ed, 1979; 1 box (Box 546)
    - Jordy, William H, 1979; 1 box (Box 546)
    - Re Keating, Kenneth B, 1979; 1 box (Box 546)
    - Kennedy, Mrs. Robert F, 1979; 1 box (Box 546)
    - Kerr, Clark, 1979; 1 box (Box 546)
    - Knopf, Alfred A, 1979; 1 box (Box 546)
    - Knoxville News-Sentinel, 1979; 1 box (Box 546)
    - Lawrence University, 1979; 1 box (Box 546)
    - Levin, Gerald M, 1979; 1 box (Box 546)
    - Lewis, Flora, 1979; 1 box (Box 546)
    - Lilienthal, Allen, 1979; 1 box (Box 546)
    - Lilienthal, David E., Jr, 1979; 1 box (Box 546)
    - Lilienthal, Theodore, 1979; 1 box (Box 546)
    - Linowitz, Sol M, 1979; 1 box (Box 546)
    - Lockwood, Mrs. William W, 1979; 1 box (Box 546)
    - Louisville Gas and Electric Co, 1979; 1 box (Box 546)
    - McCleery, William, 1979; 1 box (Box 546)
      Includes Mr. McCleery's suggestion on October 1. 1979 for a draft of the book entitled Atomic Energy: A New Start by David E. Lilienthal (1980)
    - McCloy, John J, 1979; 1 box (Box 546)
    - McNeil, Marshall, 1979; 1 box (Box 546)
    - MacLeish, Archibald, 1979; 1 box (Box 546)
    - Macy, John W. Jr, 1979; 1 box (Box 546)
    - Manny, Carter H., Jr, 1979; 1 box (Box 546)
    - Re Martha's Vineyard, 1979; 1 box (Box 546)
    - Martin, Jane, 1979; 1 box (Box 546)
    - Mead, Thomas A, 1979; 1 box (Box 547)
    - Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1979; 1 box (Box 547)
    - Meyer, Andre, 1979; 1 box (Box 547)
    - Miller, Lawrence K, 1979; 1 box (Box 547)
    - Miscellaneous, 1979; 1 box (Box 547)
    - Morgan, Lucy S, 1979; 1 box (Box 547)
    - Morse, David A, 1979; 1 box (Box 547)
    - Moyers, Bill, 1979; 1 box (Box 547)
    - Murphy, Franklin D, 1979; 1 box (Box 547)
    - Nader, Ralph, 1979; 1 box (Box 547)
    - Nashville Tennessean, 1979; 1 box (Box 547)
    - Nassau Club, 1979; 1 box
      - Princeton, New Jersey, 1979; 1 box (Box 547)
    - National Academy of Public Administration, 1979; 1 box (Box 547)
    - Re National Coal and Surface Mining Conference, 1979 November 18 - 20; 1 box (Box 547)
    - Neumann, Emanuel, 1979; 1 box (Box 547)
    - New England Electric System, 1979; 1 box (Box 547)
    - New York State, 1979; 1 box (Box 547)
    - New York Times, 1979; 1 box (Box 547)
    - New Yorker, 1979; 1 box (Box 547)
    - Nixon Newspapers, Wabash, Indiana, 1979; 1 box (Box 547)
    - Norris, Tennessee - Building Fund, 1979; 1 box (Box 547)
    - Re Nuclear Energy, 1979; 1 box (Box 547)
    - Oak Ridge Associated Universities, 1979; 1 box (Box 547)
    - Oak Ridge National Laboratory, 1979; 1 box (Box 547)
    - Oliver, John, 1979; 1 box (Box 547)
    - Opthalmic Research Foundation, 1979; 1 box (Box 547)
    - Re Oppenheimer, J. Robert, 1979; 1 box (Box 547)
    - Oriental Institute, 1979; 1 box (Box 547)
    - University of Chicago, 1979; 1 box (Box 547)
    - Overseas Development Council (O.D.C.), 1979; 1 box (Box 547)
    - Owen, Marguerite, 1979; 1 box (Box 547)
    - Re Paterson, New Jersey - Project, 1979; 1 box (Box 547)
    - Penalosa Camargo, Enrique, 1979; 1 box (Box 547)
    - Percy, Charles H, 1979; 1 box (Box 547)
    - Perkins, James A, 1979; 1 box (Box 547)
    - Re Princeton University, 1979; 1 box (Box 547)
    - Princeton University Press, 1979; 1 box (Box 547)
    - Radcliffe College, 1979; 1 box (Box 548)
    - Ray, Dixy Lee, 1979; 1 box (Box 548)
    - Reston, James, 1979; 1 box (Box 548)
    - Rhode Island Public Utilities Commission, 1979; 1 box (Box 548)
    - Rockefeller, Rodman C, 1979; 1 box (Box 548)
    - Rockefeller Public Service Awards, 1979; 1 box (Box 548)
    - Rohatyn, Felix G, 1979; 1 box (Box 548)
    - Sane Education Fund, 1979; 1 box (Box 548)
    - Schuller, Mrs. Erwin, 1979; 1 box (Box 548)
    - Schwartz, David, 1979; 1 box (Box 548)
    - Seymour, Walton, 1979; 1 box (Box 548)
    - Shelton, Barrett C, 1979; 1 box (Box 548)
    - Simon and Schuster, Inc, 1979; 1 box (Box 548)
    - Smithsonian Magazine, 1979; 1 box (Box 548)
    - Spears, Ross, 1979; 1 box (Box 548)
    - Starr, Harry, 1979; 1 box (Box 548)
    - Stetson - Dale, 1979; 1 box (Box 548)
    - Straus, Donald B, 1979; 1 box (Box 548)
    - Sulzberger, Mrs. Arthur H, 1979; 1 box (Box 548)
    - Swidler, Joseph C, 1979; 1 box (Box 548)
    - Szanton, Mrs. Jules, 1979; 1 box (Box 548)
    - Szold, Mrs. Bernard, 1979; 1 box (Box 548)
    - Re Tennessee Valley Authority, 1979; 1 box
      - (1 of 2) General, 1979; 1 box (Box 549)
      - (2 of 2) Visit of Mr. and Mrs. David E. Lilienthal, 1979 May 13 - 19; 1 box (Box 549)
    - Thomas, Franklin A, 1979; 1 box (Box 549)
    - Thurber, Mrs. James, 1979; 1 box (Box 549)
    - Tobey, Mr. and Mrs. Barney, 1979; 1 box (Box 549)
    - Tobey, David M, 1979; 1 box (Box 549)
    - Tobey, Nancy, 1979; 1 box (Box 549)
    - Tobey, William, 1979; 1 box (Box 549)
    - Tsuru, Shigeto, 1979; 1 box (Box 549)
    - Twentieth Century Fund, 1979; 1 box (Box 549)
    - Vanderbilt University, Institute for Public Policy Studies, 1979; 1 box (Box 549)
    - Wagner, Aubrey J, 1979; 1 box (Box 549)
    - Warne, William E, 1979; 1 box (Box 549)
    - Webster, Bethuel M, 1979; 1 box (Box 549)
    - Wechsler, James A, 1979; 1 box (Box 549)
    - Weinberg, Alvin M, 1979; 1 box (Box 549)
    - Wharton, Clifton R., Jr, 1979; 1 box (Box 549)
    - White, Theodore E, 1979; 1 box (Box 549)
    - Who's Who, 1979; 1 box (Box 549)
    - Wilber, Donald N, 1979; 1 box (Box 549)
    - Wilson, Carroll L, 1979; 1 box (Box 549)
    - Yale Political Union, 1979; 1 box (Box 549)
    - Abzug, Bella S, 1980; 1 box (Box 550)
    - American Academy of Arts and Sciences, 1980; 1 box (Box 550)
    - American Philosophical Society, 1980; 1 box (Box 550)
    - Ames, Amyas, 1980; 1 box (Box 550)
    - Asia Society, 1980; 1 box (Box 550)
    - Baldwin, Roger N, 1980; 1 box (Box 550)
    - Re Baruch, Bernard, 1980; 1 box (Box 550)
    - Bentley, Gerald, 1980; 1 box (Box 550)
    - Bernhard, Berl, 1980; 1 box (Box 550)
    - Bethe, Hans, 1980; 1 box (Box 550)
    - Bingham, Jonathan B, 1980; 1 box (Box 550)
    - Black, Mrs. Michael, 1980; 1 box (Box 550)
    - Bromberger, Daniel, 1980; 1 box (Box 550)
    - Bromberger, Nancy and Sylvain, 1980; 1 box (Box 550)
    - Brookings Institution, 1980; 1 box (Box 550)
    - Brown University, 1980; 1 box (Box 550)
    - Bulletin for the Atomic Scientists, 1980; 1 box (Box 550)
    - Bundy, McGeorge, 1980; 1 box (Box 550)
    - Burnett, John G, 1980; 1 box (Box 550)
    - Burrelle's Press Clipping Service, 1980; 1 box (Box 550)
    - Canfield, Cass, 1980; 1 box (Box 550)
    - Carter, Hodding III, 1980; 1 box (Box 550)
    - Center for International Environment Information, 1980; 1 box (Box 550)
    - Center of Theological Inquiry, 1980; 1 box (Box 550)
    - Century Association, 1980; 1 box (Box 550)
    - Chase, Stuart, 1980; 1 box (Box 550)
    - Clapp, Norman M, 1980; 1 box (Box 550)
    - Re Colombia, 1980; 1 box (Box 550)
    - Commager, Henry Steele, 1980; 1 box (Box 550)
    - Committee for E conomic Development, 1980; 1 box (Box 550)
    - Commonwealth Edison, 1980; 1 box (Box 550)
    - Comstock Club, 1980; 1 box (Box 550)
    - Conference Board, 1980; 1 box (Box 550)
    - Copeland, Adrian and Elise, 1980; 1 box (Box 550)
    - Council on Foreign Relations, 1980; 1 box (Box 550)
    - Cunniff, John, 1980; 1 box (Box 550)
    - Daniels, Jonathan, 1980; 1 box (Box 550)
    - Dartmouth College, 1980; 1 box (Box 550)
    - DeGiacomo, Robert J, 1980; 1 box (Box 550)
    - DePauw University, 1980; 1 box (Box 550)
    - Dilworth, J. Richardson, 1980; 1 box (Box 550)
    - Re Energy, 1980; 1 box (Box 550)
    - Engelhard Minerals and Chemicals Corporation, 1980; 1 box (Box 550)
    - Re Environment, 1980; 1 box (Box 550)
    - Flom, Joseph H, 1980; 1 box (Box 551)
    - Franklin, John C, 1980; 1 box (Box 551)
    - Freeman, S. David, 1980; 1 box (Box 551)
    - Fritz, Bernardine Szold, 1980; 1 box (Box 551)
    - Gilinsky, Victor, 1980; 1 box (Box 551)
    - Goheen, Robert F, 1980; 1 box (Box 551)
    - Golden, William T, 1980; 1 box (Box 551)
    - Gulick, Luther, 1980; 1 box (Box 551)
    - Harper & Row, 1980; 1 box (Box 551)
    - Harvard University, 1980; 1 box (Box 551)
    - Haynes, William F., Jr, 1980; 1 box (Box 551)
    - Heffner, Richard D, 1980; 1 box (Box 551)
    - Henderson, Frances, 1980; 1 box (Box 551)
    - Hough, Henry B, 1980; 1 box (Box 551)
    - Re Hydro-Electric Power, 1980; 1 box (Box 551)
    - Institute for Advanced Study, 1980; 1 box (Box 551)
    - International Basic Economy Corporation (IBEC), 1980; 1 box (Box 551)
    - Re Iran, 1980; 1 box (Box 551)
    - Iwanami Shoten, Publishers, 1980; 1 box
      - Tokyo, Japan, 1980; 1 box (Box 551)
    - Jackson, Henry M, 1980; 1 box (Box 551)
    - Jesselson, Ludwig, 1980; 1 box (Box 551)
    - Johnson, Barbara, 1980; 1 box (Box 551)
    - Jordy, William H, 1980; 1 box (Box 551)
    - Re Kastenmeier, Robert, 1980; 1 box (Box 551)
    - Kennan, George F, 1980; 1 box (Box 551)
    - Knofp, Alfred A, 1980; 1 box (Box 551)
    - Krutch, Charles, 1980; 1 box (Box 551)
    - Lawrence University, 1980; 1 box (Box 551)
    - Re Lazard Freres and Co, 1980; 1 box (Box 551)
    - Leland, Wilma S, 1980; 1 box (Box 551)
    - Leventhal, Paul L, 1980; 1 box (Box 551)
    - Levin, Gerald M, 1980; 1 box (Box 551)
    - Levy, Walter J, 1980; 1 box (Box 551)
    - Lilienthal, Allen, 1980; 1 box (Box 551)
    - Lilienthal, David E., Jr, 1980; 1 box (Box 551)
    - Lilienthal, Margaret L, 1980; 1 box (Box 551)
    - Lilienthal, Theodore, 1980; 1 box (Box 551)
    - McCleery, William, 1980; 1 box (Box 551)
    - McCord, James I, 1980; 1 box (Box 551)
    - McNamara, Robert S, 1980; 1 box (Box 551)
    - MacLeish, Archibald, 1980; 1 box (Box 551)
    - Macy, John W.,Jr, 1980; 1 box (Box 551)
    - Re Martha's Vineyard, 1980; 1 box (Box 551)
    - Martin, Jane, 1980; 1 box (Box 551)
    - Marton, Andrew, 1980; 1 box (Box 551)
    - Mead, Thomas A, 1980; 1 box (Box 551)
    - Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1980; 1 box (Box 551)
    - Re Meyer, Andre, 1980; 1 box (Box 551)
    - Miscellaneous, 1980; 1 box (Box 552)
    - Morgan, Lucy S, 1980; 1 box (Box 552)
    - National Academy of Sciences, 1980; 1 box (Box 552)
    - Re National Coal and Surface Mining Conference, 1980; 1 box (Box 552)
    - Natural Resources Defense Council, 1980; 1 box (Box 552)
    - New York Times, 1980; 1 box (Box 552)
    - Northeast Public Power Association, 1980; 1 box (Box 552)
    - Re Nuclear Energy, 1980; 1 box (Box 552)
    - Oak Ridge National Laboratory, 1980; 1 box (Box 552)
    - Obregon, Mauricio, 1980; 1 box (Box 552)
    - Ophthalmic Research Foundation, 1980; 1 box (Box 552)
    - Overseas Development Council (O.D.C.), 1980; 1 box (Box 552)
    - Pampanini, Andrea H.A., 1980; 1 box (Box 552)
    - Percy, Charles H, 1980; 1 box (Box 552)
    - Percy, Mark, 1980; 1 box (Box 552)
    - Re Princeton University, 1980; 1 box (Box 552)
    - Re Publication by David E. Lilienthal, 1980; 1 box (Box 552)
      Includes Atomic Energy: A New Start, Harper & Row, l980.
    - Radcliffe College, 1980; 1 box (Box 552)
    - Reston, James, 1980; 1 box (Box 552)
    - Rhode Island Public Utilities Commission, 1980; 1 box (Box 552)
    - Robinson, William J, 1980; 1 box (Box 552)
    - Roberts, Ann R, 1980; 1 box (Box 552)
    - Rockefeller, Rodman C, 1980; 1 box (Box 552)
    - Rostow, W.W., 1980; 1 box (Box 552)
    - Scientists' Institute for Public Information, 1980; 1 box (Box 552)
    - Shelton, Barrett C, 1980; 1 box (Box 552)
    - Sholes, Mrs. Maxwell, 1980; 1 box (Box 552)
    - Smyth, Henry D, 1980; 1 box (Box 552)
    - Spears, Ross, 1980; 1 box (Box 552)
    - Straus, Donald B, 1980; 1 box (Box 552)
    - Swidler, Joseph C, 1980; 1 box (Box 552)
    - Szanton, Peter L, 1980; 1 box (Box 552)
    - Re Tennessee Valley Authority, 1980; 1 box (Box 553)
    - Tobey, Mr. and Mrs. Barney, 1980; 1 box (Box 553)
    - Tobey, David M, 1980; 1 box (Box 553)
    - Tobey, William, 1980; 1 box (Box 553)
    - Tsuru, Shigeto, 1980; 1 box (Box 553)
    - Twentieth Century Fund, 1980; 1 box (Box 553)
    - Vanderbilt University, Institute for Public Policy Studies, 1980; 1 box (Box 553)
    - Volpe, Joseph, Jr, 1980; 1 box (Box 553)
    - Wagner, Aubrey J, 1980; 1 box (Box 553)
    - Walsh, Jerome K, 1980; 1 box (Box 553)
    - Weinberg, Alvin M, 1980; 1 box (Box 553)
    - Wells, Herman B, 1980; 1 box (Box 553)
    - Who's Who, 1980; 1 box (Box 553)
    - Wilson, Alfred, 1980; 1 box (Box 553)
    - Wilson, Carroll L, 1980; 1 box (Box 553)
    - Zeller, Robert G, 1980; 1 box (Box 553)
    - American Academy of Arts and Sciences, 1981; 1 box (Box 554)
    - Baldwin, Roger N, 1981; 1 box (Box 554)
    - Bingham, Jonathan B, 1981; 1 box (Box 554)
    - Brown University, 1981; 1 box (Box 554)
    - Canfield, Cass, 1981; 1 box (Box 554)
    - Common Cause, 1981; 1 box (Box 554)
    - Council on Foreign Relations, 1981; 1 box (Box 554)
    - DePauw University, 1981; 1 box (Box 554)
    - Re Development and Resources Corporation, 1981; 1 box (Box 554)
    - Downs, Hugh, 1981; 1 box (Box 554)
    - Re Energy, 1981; 1 box (Box 554)
    - Engelhaxd Minerals and Chemicals Corporation, 1981; 1 box (Box 554)
    - Freeman, David, 1981; 1 box (Box 554)
    - Fritz, Bernardine Szold, 1981; 1 box (Box 554)
    - International Basic Economy Corporation (IBEC), 1981; 1 box (Box 554)
    - Re Lilienthal, David E. - Death, 1981 January 15; 1 box (Box 554)
      Includes Condolences, Memorial Service, January 23, 1981, etc.
    - McMahan, Elizabeth L, 1981; 1 box (Box 554)
    - Macy, John W., Jr, 1981; 1 box (Box 554)
    - Miscellaneous, 1981; 1 box (Box 554)
    - Moses, Robert, 1981; 1 box (Box 554)
    - Nahas, Alexander F, 1981; 1 box (Box 554)
    - Re Publication by David E. Lilienthal: Atomic Energy: A New Start, Harper & Row, 1980; 1 box (Box 554)
    - Rhode Island Public Utilities Commission, 1981; 1 box (Box 554)
    - Rostow, W.W., 1981; 1 box (Box 554)
    - Roth, William V, 1981; 1 box (Box 554)
    - Spears, Ross, 1981; 1 box (Box 554)
    - Sulzberger, Mrs. Arthur H, 1981; 1 box (Box 554)
    - Re Tennessee Valley Authority, 1981; 1 box (Box 554)
      Includes items on death, January 15, 1981, of David E. Lilienthal in the Tennessee valley.
    - Twentieth Century Fund, 1981; 1 box (Box 554)
    - Weinberg, Alvin M, 1981; 1 box (Box 554)
- Series 19: Chronological Files, 1955-1979; 8 boxes
  Series 19: Chronological Files contains copies of correspondence, notes and other information collected into bound files on an annual basis.
  The materials in this series are arranged in chronological order by year. Within each bound set the materials are in reverse chronological order.
  - 1955-1956, 1 box (Box 555)
  - 1957-1959, 1 box (Box 556)
  - 1958-1960, 1 box (Box 557)
  - 1961-1963, 1 box (Box 558)
  - 1964-1965, 1 box (Box 559)
  - 1966-1967, 1 box (Box 560)
  - 1968-1972, 1 box (Box 561)
  - 1973-1979, 1 box (Box 562)
- Series 20: Appointment Books, 1950-1980; 9 boxes
  Series 20: Appointment Books consists of Lilienthal's appointment books from 1950 to 1955.
  The appointment books in this series are arranged in chronological order.
  - 1950-1952, 1 box (Box 563)
  - 1953-1955, 1 box (Box 564)
  - 1956-1958, 1 box (Box 565)
  - 1959-1961, 1 box (Box 566)
  - 1962-1966, 1 box (Box 567)
  - 1967-1972, 1 box (Box 568)
  - 1973-1976, 1 box (Box 569)
  - 1977-1980, 1 box (Box 570)
  - 1953-1955, 1 box (Box 571)
- Series 21: Financial Records: Personal, 1924-1981; 14 boxes
  Series 21: Financial Records: Personal consists of Lilienthal's personal and family financial records from 1924 to 1981.
  - undated, 1924-1939, 1 box (Box 572)
  - 1940-1949, 1 box (Box 573)
  - 1950-1951, 1 box (Box 574)
  - 1952-1953, 1 box (Box 575)
  - 1954-1958, 1 box (Box 576)
  - 1959-1964, 1 box (Box 577)
  - 1965-1968, 1 box (Box 578)
  - 1969, 1 box (Box 579)
  - 1970-1972, 1 box (Box 580)
  - 1973, 1 box (Box 581)
  - 1974, 1 box (Box 582)
  - 1975, 1 box (Box 583)
  - 1976, 1 box (Box 584)
  - 1977-1981, 1 box (Box 585)
- Series 22: Publications about or relating to David E. Lilienthal, 1950-1979; 1 box
  Series 22: Publications about or relating to David E. Lilienthal contains primarily magazine, journal, or newspaper articles and other published material that are about or relating to Lilienthal from 1950 to 1979.
  The materials in this series are arranged in chronological order by the date of publication.
  - 1950-1979, 1 box (Box 586)
- Series 23: Press Releases: Atomic Energy Commission, 1950-1961 December 28; 13 boxes
  Series 23: Press Releases: Atomic Energy Commission consists of bound files of press releases issued by the Atomic Energy Commission.
  The press releases are bound together by year. Within each file the press releases are in reverse chronological order.
  - 1950 January-1952 December, 1 box (Box 589)
  - 1953 January 8 - 1954 October 12, 1 box (Box 590)
  - 1954 October 13 - 1955 August 23, 1 box (Box 591)
  - 1955 August 28 - 1956 April 13, 1 box (Box 592)
  - 1956 April 15 - 1956 December 31, 1 box (Box 593)
  - 1957 January 2 - 1957 July 10, 1 box (Box 594)
  - 1957 July 11 - 1958 March 28, 1 box (Box 595)
  - 1958 April-1958 December, 1 box (Box 596)
  - 1951 January-1960 January, 1 box (Box 597)
  - 1960 February 3 - 1960 August 17, 1 box (Box 598)
  - 1960 August 18 - 1961 April 28, 1 box (Box 599)
  - 1961 May 1-1961 November 3, 1 box (Box 600)
  - 1961 November 6 - 1961 December 28, 1 box (Box 601)
- Series 24: Awards and Plaques, dates not examined; 2 boxes
  Series 24: Awards and Plaques contains a variety of awards and certificates given to Lilienthal throughout his career. In some cases, documents or correspondence related to a particular award is included in the file
  - Awards, dates not examined; 2 boxes (Box 606, Box 607)
- Series 25: Photographs, 1915-1979; 9 boxes
  Series 25: Photographs includes a wide variety of photographs of personal and professional events.
  The photographs in this series are roughly in chronological order where the dates of the photographs are known.
  - 1918-1939, 1 box (Box 610)
  - 1940-1945, 1 box (Box 611)
  - 1946-1949, 1 box (Box 612)
  - 1950-1969, 1 box (Box 613)
  - 1970-1979, undated; 1 box (Box 614)
  - A-Z by subject or person, undated; 1 box (Box 615)
  - Yearbooks 1915-1916 and undated photographs (ML-1997-03], 1 box (Box 615)
  - Signed portrait photos, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 616)
  - Group photographs, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 617)
  - Oversize photographs, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 618)
- Series 26: Reference Books, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 621)
  Series 26: Reference Books includes miscellaenous government documents and reports collected by Lilienthal during the course of his career.
  The materials in this series are in no particular order.
- Series 27: Foreign Editions and Other Publications, dates not examined; 2 boxes (Box 622, Box 623)
  Series 27: Foreign Editions and Other Publications includes mostly foreign editions of Lilienthal's publications.
  The publications in this series are in no particular order.
- Series 28: Books by Others Inscribed to David E. Lilienthal, undated; 1 box
  Series 28: Books by Others Inscribed to David E. Lilienthal includes books published by other authors and given or presented to Lilienthal and inscribed to him.
  - Books by Others Inscribed to David E. Lilienthal, undated; 1 box (Box 624)
- Series 29: Card Files, undated; 6 boxes
  Series 29: Card Files consists of index cards of Lilienthal's personal and professional contact information as well as an old card index to his correspondence, kept with the papers as a finding aid before they were moved to the Seeley G. Mudd Manuscript Library.
  Arranged in the order it was received
  - Surname A-Z, undated; 3 boxes (Box 625, Box 626, Box 627)
  - State A-Va, undated; 2 boxes (Box 628, Box 629)
    Arranged by state and in some cases by region or city within each state, and within each location alphabetical by last name of contact.
  - Correspondents A-Z, undated; 1 box (Box 630)
    Kept as finding with the Lilienthal Papers at Firestone Library before they were moved to the Seeley G. Mudd Manuscript Library with reference to box numbers
- Series 30: Additional Papers, dates not examined; 1 box
  Series 30: Additional Papers includes additional correspondence and publications not included in earlier series.
  - Correspondence, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 631)
  - Publications, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 631)